Jonida Baci

Web Developer

PHONE +355-694718883 EMAIL jonida.baci99@outlook.com ADDRESS Tirana, Albania Contact

SKILLS

FRONTEND

JavaScript | React Js | CSS | HTML6 | Nuxt/ Next Js

RACKEND

C | C++ | C# | PHP | Python

TOOLS

Azure Devops | Bitbucket | Github | Git | Gitlab | Visual Code | Visual Studio Code 2022

FRFAMEWORKS

Ionic | Kendo Ui | Prime Faces

LANGUAGES

Albanian | English | Italian

FIND ME

You can find more about me in these links

- **GITHUB**
- LINKEDIN
- MY WEBSITE

PROFILE SUMMARY

I'm Jonida Baci, a frontend developer.

I am well-versed developer in React JS and Vanilla Javascript and have worked with frameworks such as Ionic, Kendo, and Prime Faces for both web and mobile applications. My experience in Bootstrap, Next JS, and Vue JS demonstrates my versatility as a developer, and my self-study and online courses have given me knowledge in Python, C#, and Unity for game and backend development.

Additionally, I have experience as a WordPress developer, crafting responsive web pages using HTML5 and CSS3, and creating plugins with PHP. I am also proficient in Figma.

EDUCATION

Sep 2018 -Jul 2021

Bachelor in Computer Science: Informatics

University of Tirana, FSHN

Studied in key areas such as C/C++, Java development, Oracle Database, Operating systems, computer networking, computer architecture, language theory, and software engineering.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2022 -Present

Web Developer Commit Software, Italy/ Tirana

- Developing mobile and web applications using technologies, including Vanilla JavaScript, Vue.js, Nuxt.js and mostly React Js with frameworks such as Ionic, Kendo UI, and Prime Faces.
- Designed, tested, developed, and maintained both new and existing projects .

Jan 2021 -Dec 2021

WordPress Developer Intermedia, Tirana

- Created responsive web pages with WordPress, JavaScript, HTML5 and CSS3.
- My expertise extends to cross-browser compatibility and search engine optimization (SEO) Created custom plugins using PHP

COURSES

Course on Introduction to Video Games Creation

XAMK Open University - Finland

 Through this course, I have acquired knowledge in various software packages including Krita and Blender, as well as proficiency in C# coding within the Unity framework diving into the creation, building, and coding processes of videogame development.

The Complete JavaScript Course 2023: From Zero to Expert!

Jonas Schmedtmann - Udemy

INDIVIDUAL PROJECTS

Demos of some projects i did during my learning progress

- RECIPE APP
- BANK USER INTERFACE
- SIMPLE GUESS THE NUMBER GAME
- DICE GAME

 From this course I got fundamental knowledge of JavaScript, modern ES6+ concepts, higher order functions, asynchronous JavaScript including Event loop, promises, async/await, AJAX calls, APIs, and modern tools such as NPM, Parcel, and ES6 modules for 2022 and beyond.